Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
The first test is now over.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
Six parties—eighteen individuals—
have passed the first test.
The second test will take place
three days from now.
You will be informed of the details later.
That's all. You are dismissed.
You're there like the wind
Closing your eyes at sunset
I wonder what's on your mind
With your eyelids open
Your eyes shone like glass
It faintly smelled like a sunny day
Clear up the sky, let flowers bloom
Bloom and blame it on the sunny sky
Even the rain, when it stops
Will make you shine in the sunlight
Calm the stirring sounds in my heart
We go like the sunny wind
Go on and fly over that cloud
Further and further away
It's evening, huh?
Lazing around isn't half bad.
What's going on?
Coming.
Fern? I thought you were at
the first-class mage exam.
The first test is over.
We returned last night.
Mr. Stark, you know it's evening, don't you?
What?
You were asleep, weren't you?
Did you stay up all night?
Yes.
What else?
I drank juice in the middle of the night.
Sorry! I'm sorry, okay?
Uh-oh. You made her angry.
Ms. Frieren, you only just woke up, too.
Caught in the crossfire.
Looks like we'll be spending
the day making Fern happy.
What should we do?
Let's get something good to eat.
Something good?
It's a bit expensive,
but I found a nice place when I came here
before with Himmel and the others.
Wasn't that over eighty years ago?
Will it still be there?
Oh, my.
The lantern lit up.
I told you it was an easy fix.
Thank you as always, Richter.
Sure thing.
I know. You're welcome to have these.
I'll see you later.
Grandma, I'm not a kid anymore.
I'm a middle-aged man.
To an old woman like me,
you're still a child.
You like those, don't you?
Sorry, but the shop is closed.
A crazy old man dragged me into a fistfight.
I need to rest.
Sounds rough, Richter.
Why don't we get something
to eat together, then?
There's a restaurant we're looking for,
but Laufen and I don't know the area.
Laufen, what are you doing
with Denken, anyway?
And where'd you get that thing you're eating?
The old man bought these for me.
I'm not sharing.
What are you, his granddaughter?
Now, leave. We're no longer a party.
You don't know how to get
along in the world, do you?
If you intend to live as a mage, then
ingratiating yourself to me wouldn't hurt.
There are plenty of places
to eat around here.
Just choose one.
My wife and I...
Before she passed away,
we visited a restaurant together.
I've never forgotten the taste of their food.
You'd better be paying.
Of course I am.
I told you, it can't hurt.
Four-eyes.
Übel.
It's nice to finally meet you.
You don't use a clone when you're in town?
If you just want to make small talk,
do you mind if we walk?
That's fine, but if you try to run
away from me, I might kill you.
Can I ask you something?
You don't think anything
of killing people, do you?
Why didn't you kill Wirbel?
You had the opportunity, didn't you?
You were watching?
Nothing gets past you, huh?
It's hard to explain.
I'm surprised.
Your hands are already drenched in blood,
and yet you still want to remain human.
That's right. I use this time
to prepare myself to kill.
Maybe it's because I empathized with him.
It made me want to put off
the killing blow, too.
I can't move. What is this?
Sorganeil.
It's a spell that binds whoever I'm looking at.
The magic a person specializes in
is strongly related to their life and nature.
I've always been this way.
Empathizing with someone
allows me to use their spells,
and I can't use the spells of anyone
I can't empathize with.
Four-eyes, your clones are such
perfect copies of yourself
that they're capable of everything you are.
What goes through that head of yours?
What kind of life have you led?
Tell me.
I see.
You use magic by feel.
The type of mage who casts spells without
understanding the principles behind them.
I don't like dim-witted people like you.
That doesn't answer my question.
I'm saying I won't tell you
because I don't like you.
I don't mind if you kill me,
though you'll never get another chance
to empathize with me if you do.
I'll pass. I think I understand you
a little better now.
Oh?
I think I'd like to know more.
Where were you headed?
Who knows? Don't follow me.
This is it.
You've got a good eye, Denken.
This is the best restaurant in town.
I come here all the time.
My wife and I visited
this place fifty years ago.
Looks like it hasn't changed.
How curious.
Really?
You're sure I can order
as many desserts as I want?
Sure.
Denken, it's Frieren.
What should I get?
I recommend...
It's not my birthday.
Can I really indulge myself like this?
Leave them be. They look
like they're having fun.
Meals should be enjoyed.
We're here for the same reason, after all.
All right. Time to stuff myself.
That's a ton of food, huh?
Ms. Frieren, you like to eat like
this sometimes, don't you?
Thank you for returning the heirloom knife
the demons took from me.
I, Lecker, the greatest chef of the century,
shall provide you with the ultimate service
and reward you however I can.
That's a lot of food, isn't it?
The food here is good.
We'd better savor everything we can.
You still don't need to eat so much at once.
There's always next time.
I thought so, too, but there are many flavors
I've never been able to experience again.
Don't worry, Ms. Frieren.
This restaurant's flavors will live on
through future generations.
They'll still be around 100
or even 200 years from now.
I see. It's interesting, isn't it?
All chefs say that.
Then they try to leave their mark
by changing the flavors of past dishes.
If that happens, we can simply find
even more delicious flavors.
Forgive me, Mr. Himmel, but there are
no flavors in this world greater than mine.
Then you'd better make sure
they last into the future.
That's the reward I ask for this job.
If that is your wish, Hero, then I shall do
what no chef has done before.
Frieren, this is really good!
Does anyone deserve to be this happy?
Seriously? Despite all he said,
the flavors have changed.
But now I don't have to
look for tastier flavors.
It's way better now than it was back then.
It really is good.
You have food on your cheek, Mr. Stark.
You must eat your vegetables, too.
You're totally acting like her grandfather.
Huh. You're a lighter eater than I expected.
What's wrong with that?
That was delicious, Ms. Frieren.
I'm glad she's in a better mood.
By the way, how's our money situation?
I used up my savings.
This is the state of nothingness.
You've arrived at the essence of martial arts.
There is nothing left for me to teach you.
Who was that old man?
I don't know.
He comes to talk to me when I'm training.
You seem to attract a lot of weird people.
Well, whatever. Do you have a minute?
I'd like your help with something.
What happened?
The heck? She's super pissed off.
She's in an even worse mood than yesterday.
I know.
What did you do?
It was my turn to go shopping today,
but I overslept.
You do that all the time.
Why would she get mad about it now?
Fern is the type to let things
build up until she explodes.
What happens when she explodes?
She gives me the silent treatment.
Do you have to fight like children?
Please, Stark. I need you to mediate for us.
She won't talk to me.
What? No way. I'm too scared.
You're right. Sorry.
That was an unreasonable ask.
Listen, Ms. Fern.
She's sorry for what she did.
I want to eat.
What?
I want to eat snacks.
She's such a pain in the butt.
Then let's go buy some together.
I wonder if I've got any savings left.
Huh? Isn't he...
Wirbel of the Northern Magic Corps, right?
You're a warrior, aren't you?
Huh? What do you want?
What do you think?
Huh? What?
He won't do.
I wonder what he's up to.
Thanks for waiting, Kanne.
You're looking cuter than ever, Lawine.
My brothers are home
from the imperial capital.
They always buy crap I don't need.
I'm not their dress-up doll.
My mom's really into it, too.
She made no effort to stop them.
You're even more spoiled than me.
If that's what you think,
then let's trade places.
It's hell being compared
to my talented brothers.
Come on, let's go. This outfit is so stifling.
Then allow me to escort you today,
Little Miss Lawine.
Ow, ow! You're gonna rip them off!
Um, Ms. Fern. What would you like?
Anything is fine. You can choose, Mr. Stark.
She only says that when
she wants something specific.
What should we do?
Don't ask me.
Hey, isn't that Frieren?
Yeah.
I'm glad we ran into you.
We were just thinking about
visiting you at the inn.
Who are they?
We were in the same party
during the first test.
Frieren was really helpful.
Also, she was like a teacher.
Oh?
Because you two wouldn't stop fighting.
It's Lawine's fault.
Ow, ow!
I don't feel comfortable
being surrounded by girls.
Now, now.
Hey.
What?
You're a warrior, aren't you?
Huh?
What? H-Hey...
Stop. Wh-What's this about?
You're great.
What's going on?
The Continental Magic Association
has hired me to eliminate a Fresser
that's been ravaging crops.
I'm looking for a front-liner.
We met during the test, right?
Is he your friend? Can I borrow him?
Go right ahead.
How could you?
He's taking your friend away.
Are you okay with this?
It'll be fine. He had no ill intentions.
I could hardly believe he was the same person.
He's probably the type who can
turn it on and off for work.
My brothers are like that, too.
Here, Frieren.
Thank you.
I didn't do anything to deserve your thanks.
No.
If not for you, we wouldn't have
advanced to the second test.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Himmel.
There's nothing to worry about now.
Yeah.
Go on. Your parents are waiting for you.
Okay.
Himmel, why do you help people?
Because I'm a hero.
That's not what I meant.
Well, maybe I do it for myself.
Maybe it's because I want
people to remember me.
To live is to be known
and remembered by others.
What should I do to be remembered?
Change someone's life,
even just in a small way.
That's probably enough.
Anyway, then Lawine...
No, that was you, Kanne.
What? Is that right?
There was that other time, too. Remember?
Ms. Frieren, these sweets
they gave us are really good.
You're finally feeling better.
Come to think of it, Frieren struggled
to get up on the morning of the second day.
Don't talk about that.
You'll sour her mood again.
Hmph.
Frieren.
Typically, the first-class mage exam
consists of three tests.
Next time, we'll be enemies.
That's true.
What's that?
It's a notification of the next test.
There's the location and date
of the second test,
as well as the proctor's name.
The proctor is Sense, huh?
Our luck just ran out.
Aw, man. And after we passed
the first test and everything.
What do you mean?
Sense has proctored four tests in the past.
Not a single person passed any of them.
This meat is good.
You're incredible. You demonstrated
the essence of martial arts!
You've put together a dreadful test.
You think so?
I'm a pacifist, Genau,
unlike you.
And I'm alright
Yeah, I hear you
The wind teases this hair that's longer now
There's meaning in everything
Even the days that came to a halt
Now that I finally understand,
I've caught up to you
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
I won't ask to see you, so at least
Let me remember the past, just for today
So, if we were to meet again
No more hesitations, I'd choose the present
Anytime, anywhere, yah
Anytime, anywhere
I'll be there (close your eyes,
and I'll always be there)
Even if there are no absolutes
I'm always aware of your thoughts
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
I wasn't expecting to encounter these here.
It's a gargoyle!
It's a mimic.
Brutal. It doesn't even leave bones behind.
I can't agree to that.
It must be the work of demons or monsters.
We'll proceed with caution
while mapping the dungeon.
They must be terrifyingly powerful.
For the second test,
you will be raiding a dungeon.